couponingforfreebies.com 2018-11-14

# Privacy Policy - Couponing for Freebies

## Who we are

Hi, my name is Crystal and I am the owner of Couponing for Freebies website address is: http://couponingforfreebies.com. This Privacy Policy below will tell you in detail of what data this site collects and what it is used for.

If you need to contact me you can send me an email to (me @ couponingforfreebies.com)

**Note that this Privacy Policy can be revised from time to time and will always be done on this page. The last update being May 24th, 2018. By using this site you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.**

## What personal data we collect and why.

When you visit my site I automatically collect personal info such as,

  * Your IP address (aka Internet Protocol addresses)
  * Type of browser you use.
  * Your ISP (aka Internet Service Provider)
  * The time, date and length of your visit.
  * The pages you visit on this site.
  * The site you came from and go to when you leave the site

All of that data is collected and stored using Google Analytics (You can read Google’s privacy policy at: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). I collect it for administrative purposes so that I can see what types of things people like the most such as recycling, gardening, recipes and so on. Knowing the types of content that is most liked and from what areas helps me better understand what content to keep posting. I don’t want to waste your time or mine so it is better to narrow it down.

## Comments

When you comment on this site I do ask for your name and email address. That is so I know the name of the person to replay to and if need be email you with a follow up if the answer cannot be covered in the comment area. When your comment publishes, it will show your name but not your email.

You do have the right to comment without filling in the name, email or website if you choose to do so. It will still, however, collect your IP address and browser.

We collect the IP and, ISP and browser to help detect spam from bots and other abusive users.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture (if you have one) is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

## Cookies

We use cookies on this site. A cookie is small bits of data that are stored on your browser. There are two different types of cookies, a session cookie that will expire when you close your browser, and persistent cookie, which will stay on your browser until you delete it. These are used to provide you with a more personalized experience, analyze site traffic, and serve targeted advertisements.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

Most browsers do allow you to control the use of cookies and to delete cookies. You can visit the website of the browser you use for information on how to block and delete cookies. However, you deactivate the setting of cookies in your Internet browser, not all functions of this Website may be entirely usable.

## Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## Who we share your data with

We may share your information that we collect with trusted third parties. You do have the right to opt out of the sharing of your personal data. Each third-party service provider’s use of your information is dictated by their own privacy policies.

This website currently uses the following third-party service providers:

  * Google Analytics – for collecting analytics data.  (You can read Google’s privacy policy at: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

This third party list may be amended from time to time in this website’s sole discretion.

Unless required by law, I will not sell, distribute, or reveal your personally identifiable information without your consent. However, we may disclose or transfer personal information that we have collected, to third parties if acquired all or a portion of our business. This may be from a result of a merger, consolidation, or purchase or in connection with any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding brought by or against us.

## Anonymous Data

I may from time to time use anonymous data, that does not identify you alone to provide to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Such anonymous data may include analytics or information collected from cookies.

## Advertising

Display Ads – We use third-party advertising companies such as Google to serve content and advertisements when you visit this site. They may use cookies, as noted above.

## Affiliate Program Participation

I do engage in affiliate marketing. This is done by using tracking links on this site. When you click on an affiliate link, a cookie will be placed on your browser. This will track any purchases you make for purposes of commissions.

## What rights you have over your data

Access, Update or Delete – You can at any time send an email to (me @ couponingforfreebies.com) to have the data we have collected from you (if any) accessed, have it updated or deleted.

## Sensitive Personal Information

At no time should you ever submit sensitive personal information to this Website. Sensitive personal information includes social security number, race or ethnic origin, criminal background, religious beliefs, health information, and so on. If you choose to submit such information to us, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy and the Couponing for Freebies site has no responsibility or liability for such information.

## Children’s Privacy

My website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 16 years old or older. By using this site you agree that you are at least 16 years of age or older. We do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 16 years of age.

_This policy was last updated on May_ 24th _, 2018_

You may also want to read our [Disclosure Policy](http://couponingforfreebies.com/disclosure-policy/).
